This love in my heart,
it will burn on forever.
Granting me courage, I
hope that we'll never stop.
No matter where you
are, nothing is too far.
With our everlasting bones,
we'll reach it, we are home.
I'm so
truly grateful.
I ran into you on that day so long ago.
We laughed every moment
with tears in our eyes.
Till we knew we weren't alone.
The blowing wind came in
and joined us on our way.
And with it I know we'll rise.
We'll be flying up high.
Why, tell me why are you giving up?
Why, tell me why you want to fight alone?
Hey, what kind of future
do you think you have?
Your dream is already in your hands.
This love in my heart,
it will burn off forever.
Granting me courage, I
hope it will never stop.
I don't matter where you
are, nothing is too far.
With our everlasting
paths, we'll reach it.
We are home.
On the horizon, out on
the edge of the world.
There is a place that
I want to take you to.
Let's head for it then.
But as for the way we already know.
We promised it long ago.
You scream by your voice.
That can't break through the silence.
Feeling defeated.
It crushes your helpless heart.
I've got your back, I swear.
I'll always be here.
Let's put our fate within
this light under the sun.
Can you close your eyes and
just listen to my voice?
Let's find the answer together.
I'm telling you.
In our path, I trust that it will lead us.
To another sea untarded.
Cause now we are home.
On the horizon, out on
the edge of the world.
There is a place that I wanna take you to.
Let's head forth and.
But as for the way, we already know.
We promised it long ago.
Chowbro, it's hot!
What do I do?
Now that'll be enough whining out of you,
little lady I don't like eating humans.
But a mink, that might be worth a shot.
Don't eat me!
I'm not yummy at all!
Just let her go, Barrel! Stop it!
Carrot's not gonna taste good anyway!
She's not a real rabbit, you know!
Oh, really?
Well...
Maybe I will pass the...
Whee!
If you really think I'm gonna let her go,
keep your mouth shut, you big furball.
You will be joining mama's
collection of freaks soon enough.
Freaks, what does that mean?
Strange creatures.
You'll fit right in,
I assure you,
okay
so far.
Everything is going according to plan.
I made sure to be in heavy
point when she chained me up,
so I can escape in an
instant by transforming.
I really goofed out now.
Hey, Joe's going to scold me.
It's been six hours since I
used Monster Point yesterday,
so I've got that in my arsenal, too.
Smell that?
I think the broth's ready for some mink.
Oh, Chobro!
Now's my chance.
Here it is.
They say that books
contain infinite worlds
and i'm inclined to
agree this one contains
a man-eating lion with a human face very
rare a manticore it's
called it used to live in
impelled down but when blackbeard attacked
the prison two years
ago this little darling
escaped lord glove it
moved and this one here
is my pride enjoy isn't
it beautiful uh but it's
alive in the book indeed
just as they appear
and these beasts will
never age a day as it
should be the contents
of a book have no right
to go changing themselves
behind one's back
this library is full of
creatures from around
the world oddities of every shape and eyes
tucked away from my
perusal sweet all thanks
to the extraordinary
power of my son mont door
we recently picked up a
real-life centaur from
punk hazard we even found
a griffin in the south blue
and then there's this one a long limbs
human someone help let me out humans too
big mom there's something i
couldn't help but notice your
country here is graced by people
of many races but of course
this is my dream after all all
the races living in harmony
yes but there's one race that
i haven't seen at all and
i can't help wondering about
it and i think i would notice
if they were here the giant
tribe I mean I've seen some
very large humans but that's
all for a country founded on
diversity I'm curious about
the omission is there a reason
how funny somehow you seem to miss
them well i haven't been here long
yes what is it we um uh
captured the enemy uh
we brought them here
and the two of them from
that crew?
Very well then.
Will you excuse me?
Quite the busy day.
The weather's
rotten, but make yourself at home, please.
What's wrong?
Well, I got nervous.
Didn't
think I'd get to see the
real Germa double six.
Reiju and Ichiji look so cool.
I'm a Big fan, that's all.
Getting so worked up over
a little comic strip.
Who cares if they look flashy or not?
I'm calling the shots, not Germa.
Let's see, what page was it?
It's page 55.
55.
Yep.
There.
I lick the look on their
foolish little faces.
Lickety.
How long are you gonna keep us like this?
Let me take a shower at
least, I'm covered in syrup.
It's disgusting that sounds lickety
sweet if you ask me, candy girl.
You can complain to mama.
A
transponder
snail.
Well, hello there, Straw Hat.
It's been a little while.
I commend your effort making it this far.
Is this big, Mom?
Let me out now!
I gotta go wait for Saji!
And I'll wreck your whole
damn island if I have to!
My goodness, you've still
got some spirit, don't you?
I was disappointed to see you
didn't bring your whole crew.
You had some bold words
for me on Fisherman Island.
Or have you forgotten about that?
Once I get there, I'm gonna kick your ass.
Then I'll make Fisherman
Island my territory.
Yeah, I'm still gonna
kick your ass someday.
Right now, we're only here
to take Soji back with us.
I think I've heard enough
of your meaningless bluffs.
Shut up, you're just hiding from me.
Come show yourself if you're so tough.
I'll fight you, right here and right now.
Hey!
Are you scared?
Is that it?
Come face me!
I'm ready for a fight!
Don't push your luck.
You're nothing but a rookie.
You haven't even spent
a year in the new world.
And you request an
audience with an emperor?
Learn your place.
Besides, my officers are more than capable
of killing you without my assistance.
Let's make a deal, Straw Hat.
I'm willing to be generous and let
you waltz out of here with your life,
but you have to give up on Sanji.
Go to hell!
Sanji and Pudding's
wedding is important to me.
It must go smoothly, so I
can't have you ruining things.
While we're having fun,
you'll sit there quietly, and we'll see
how I'm feeling once this is all over.
Nothing to say?
Good!
Because if you spoil what I've been looking
forward to, I'll really make you suffer.
You'll wish that you were dead.
That reminds me, remember when we
first spoke down on Fishman Island?
You ate all of the candies
that were supposed to be mine,
then you offered the
stash of treasure you got
from King Neptune in an
attempt to appease me.
I'll make you a deal—we've
got a bunch of treasure.
If
I give it to you, then
can we call it even?
even
Do you know what we found in there?
Something very special.
It's too late to ask for it back.
Fishman Island's legendary treasure
chest passed down for generations.
It's called the Temate Box.
I was surprised, surely Neptune
must have given it up by accident.
It's a national treasure, you know!
I can't wait to see
what secrets are inside.
Nothing beats a
good treasure chest.
I always say so.
I'll forgive you for
stealing my candy when
everyone's gathered for
the wedding tomorrow!
I'll open the tomate box at last.
I'm gonna have so much fun!
You won't have fun at all!
Cassidy's coming back with me! Hmm?
Damn it!
Oh, yeah!
I wanna see Pudding!
Let me talk to her!
She's friends with my crew! Huh?
Pudding's your friend?
Nonsense!
Any daughter of mine would
clearly be your enemy!
That's enough babble from you,
speaking of which young lady?
I heard you killed my other daughter.
Lola, what are you talking about?
Why would I want to kill her?
She gave me your Vivra card.
Is the token of our friendship anyway?
I'm signing the piece
of my mama's Vivra card,
so if you're ever in trouble
you can use it to find
her and she'll help you
out if that ever happens.
Be sure to tell her.
I'm doing fine.
Okay, wow!
Thanks, Lola!
Lola's doing fine out there.
That was her message.
I've done my part.
All that she told me was
that her mother was a pirate.
I wasn't expecting one
of the four emperors.
Lola said that if I was in trouble to
show you the Vivra card and you'd help me.
I would never do a damn thing for her!
Oh, she's fine, is she?
Who the hell cares?
I don't want her dead!
If you know where I can find
her, you better tell me.
She's got an assassination coming her way.
Mark my words, that idiot
still thinks of us as family.
What a joke.
A child who doesn't respect her
parents' wishes is useless to me.
Little ingrate,
she spurned the most profitable political
marriage I've ever set up
and ran off like a fool.
She'll pay.
Mark my words.
Lastly and most importantly, I
will allow one of you to marry me.
The only woman Absalom is
allowed to marry is me!
You make a cute couple.
You should totally hook it up, girlfriend.
Huh? You think?
I came here to save you
because we're friends.
Loa, no!
It really is you, Loa!
I'm so glad we can meet again.
I hope so, too.
If you see my mama, tell
her I said hi, Namizo!
I didn't know I was so close
She ruined it.
If she just got married as I said, do you
have any clue how powerful I would be?
I'd have conquered them
all Kaido and Whitebeard
and red-haired Jinx would
have fallen before me.
If it wasn't for her I'd
already be king of the pirates
Cat burglar Nami, you're
gonna help me kill Lola.
You'll tell me where she is,
or I'll beat it out of you.
You're making stupid excuses, Big Mom.
Lola didn't get married,
and that's on her.
You haven't become king of the pirates,
and that's on you; nothing else to it.
Get over here and fight me!
I'm not backing down, even
if you are an emperor!
I'm taking Sanji back no matter what;
I'm gonna turn this all
around and make you sorry!
What is going on out there?
Click.
Baron Tamago! Help!
It's the intruder!
The tiger mink's totally
wrecking up the place!
Don't you mean jaguar mink?
Pedro, so you've already
infiltré le Shit? Calic. Hold on!
I'm not done with you!
He sure is funny, huh?
How do you think that would go?
You've got no bargaining chips
and you're deep in mama's Shit.
Come on, let me out.
Fight me if you're so tough.
What now?
What's up, fam?
Coming through, coming through.
Hey, unglaze, what's going on?
We got trouble at the treasure room.
We got an intruding coming
through an intruder.
You must mean, yeah, that I did my
job, but I ain't brushing my teeth.
No way, not today.
Everyone, please get out
of here while you can.
Don't let him get away!
Hurry up!
He's made fools of us enough already!
I think he moved you the other whole way!
Guess it's time.
Soul King coming to you live
from the Whole Cake Shit.
Ladies and gentlemen,
let's get ready to rock!
You're not mad, Mama? Really?
Because of that squirt?
Why do I care if he wants to bite me?
Why be angry, Zeus?
There's so much to look forward to!
Now it's in my sight.
Finally I'll have germ as mine.
And then the tomate box
will be good and mine.
Don't forget the cake.
I deserve only the finest cake there is.
Don't you think?
When I just think of tomorrow.
It washes away all my sorrows.
With a plan this good, there's
no way that I'd be back.
A joyous day, I'm on my way.
Happy day.
I'm getting a signal.
Hey, there's an intruder
near the repository.
The treasure room?
Time for the wedding cake.
Only the finest.
I bet the rotten bastard is
trying to nab my tomate box.
Who is it, huh?
It's fine.
It's fine, dammit.
Luffy and the others won't be hurt.
Big Mom promised me that.
If I get married, the
Baratie will be fine too.
Of course I don't want
to leave my friends.
But at least no one will die.
That's all that matters.
Why can't I be grateful?
Pudding is all I've got.
I can't make her sad.
Gotta put on a smile for her.
If you decide to marry
me, I won't let it be hell
Who could hurt a sweet girl like that?
I'd have to be some kind of monster.
I'll make you happy,
Press, don't you worry.
Just regular Sanji.
You know me, the romantic chef, right?
Morning!
My sweet bride!
I won't let you down!
I'll shower you with love!
Lola? Really? Indeed.
Seems the Straw Hat Girl
got a Vivre card from her,
so the homies in the
forest couldn't fight back.
She had them working for her.
By the way,
I hate to break this to you,
but Mama rejected the wedding
dress you picked out yesterday.
She'll expect you to wear the
one she picked out instead.
Mama planned out everything
after the wedding as well.
I'll show you the itinerary.
Lady Pudding, it's
still raining out there.
What's on her mind?
Pudding, as long as you do what you're
told, everything will work out just fine.
Think of yourself as my little doll,
because that's all you are, Pudding.
Be a good girl. Okay.
Don't worry, Mama would never kill me.
We're family, aren't we?
But I want to choose who I marry.
You'll understand someday.
How could they let something like this
happen the day before the tea party?
That's him! Get ready!
He's fast!
You're going down on whoever you are!
YAAAAAAAH! Huh!
Shoot him!
Fire! Hurry!
Run away!
So where is he now?
He went downstairs.
He's on the third floor of the Red
Bean Bomb Cake, near the courtyard.
He's a slippery little
miscreant, isn't he?
Try to go to him as a guy
that's evil play. Roger.
I think that's enough guards
for me for a whole lifetime.
You finally decided to face us, did you?
Well, all things considered, I
suppose I shouldn't complain.
They'd all thinned him out considerably.
huh I've never seen a creature like
you we got all sorts of things here in
this country but you are one-of-a-kind
oh I agree can't wait to show you to mama
C 'est bon, General, c 'est bon!
There's only one entrance
to the room, after all.
And if he doesn't manage to steal that
dresser, he won't be able to escape you.
Et l 'ençon sera sans ça!
As long as you guard that dark loosely,
everything should be too charmant.
Sounds simple enough. Count on me.
But let's assume he beats the guards.
When he comes out and tries to
escape, should I kill him? No, no!
The man in question is un skeleton.
Mama will want him, be sure.
Beat him, but don't kill him.
No problem.
Pedro told me all about you.
You're infused with human souls
courtesy of Big Mom's remarkable power.
That means I know what
makes you soldiers tick.
And it's the power of soul, baby!
You're not powerful, aren't you?
You're too big at all!
We've got him on the run!
Take him out!
No way to run!
You're done for!
Let's not be cruel.
Just wait.
It'll be good.
Gentlemen, please wait!
Huh?
What the hell was that?
Do you happen to know what
my stage name is, baby?
What you got, it ain't real, Snow.
It runs away, scared, that
sloppy, slapped-on, spirity horse.
When you hear my soul scream, it
knocks you off your feet, baby.
How long are you going to keep this up?
Oh!
Fancy seeing you here!
What's the occasion, Pudding?
Pudding?
Good! It's you!
Now get us out of here!
Luffy, stop!
This guy is making me mad!
You can't talk with the enemy right here!
You're being very quiet, Pudding.
Can I help you?
Could you open the book?
I just needed to say something to
Luffy and Nami before the wedding.
I don't really get it, but okay.
Whatever floats your boat.
Alright, I'll put in a bookmark.
Pudding.
This has gone all wrong!
Hey, what gives?
We went to the coast, like you said.
Cut it out!
You're gonna get him in trouble, dummy!
You're all beaten up.
Muffy.
Nami.
My brothers and sisters.
They've done terrible things to you.
I'm so sorry.
No, it's...
I'm sorry I couldn't make it
to the coast like I promised.
This is all my fault.
We don't blame you!
Just pick up your head, okay?
What are they whispering about?
I can't hear them.
Truth is...
I met with Sanji, and he proposed to me.
He made me so happy.
But still.
I know Sanji only said
that to be nice to me.
It's not what he really wants.
The truth is.
I'm just causing everyone trouble.
Now don't say that!
But you don't have to worry.
I'm not
going to marry him.
Listen.
Hey, Pudding, wait!
Well, goodbye.